http://xorsyst.com/privacy-policy/

Trending
Live Japanese Streaming TV!
November 3, 2018
0KeyHoleTV: Watch Live Japanese TV Online!
10
Main menuNewsNewsNewsEverything we know about Detective Pikachu!November 12, 20180Read more
Barak Obama, Taro Aso, and the Internet November 18, 2008
Translate Japanese feeds in Google Reader November 12, 2008AnimeAnimeAnimeVideosDragon Ball Super – Broly MovieOctober 3, 2018Read more
Ningin’s 8 Days of Anime! September 18, 2008
How to make your own fansubs September 4, 2008CosplayCosplayCosplayWorld Cosplay Summit 2008August 4, 2008Read more
A Marine Corps Cafe in Japan June 4, 2008
A-kon 19 breaks Guinness World Record June 3, 2008GamesGamesGamesJapanKids vs ZombiesMay 5, 2009Read more
Jackie Chan in Street Fighter? September 30, 2008
Top 25 Capcom Characters of All Time September 30, 2008JapanJapanFoodJapanPerfect yakitori from a machine?January 17, 20190Read more
Japan unveils a Nutella vending machine! November 9, 20180
Live Japanese Streaming TV! HotNovember 3, 20180
Want to live in a haunted house? October 31, 20180
Kirby Cafe – Delicious Kirby inspired food October 22, 20181
KeyHoleTV: Watch Live Japanese TV Online! HotOctober 20, 2018
Robo-Geisha is one crazy movie July 3, 2009IdolsIdolsIdolsJapanese Idols Try English AccentJanuary 7, 20190Read more
Reika Saiki is stronger than you! November 5, 20180
BoA tries to conquer American pop industry September 11, 2008
Yuko Ogura wins Gravure Idol Award July 18, 2008
Top 10 Japanese Gravure Idols HotJuly 3, 2008
Miyuki Asao suicide by hydrogen sulfide May 10, 2008
Who is Xiaxue? April 24, 2008VideosVideosVideosJust how heavy are boobs?November 6, 20180Read more
Japanese Homer in the new Simpsons intro February 16, 2009
Super Mario saves the day January 15, 2009TwitchVodsPrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyEffective date: October 1, 2018xorsyst.com (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the http://www.xorsyst.com website (the “Service”).This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data. Our Privacy Policy for xorsyst.com is managed through Free Privacy Policy.We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from http://www.xorsyst.comInformation Collection And UseWe collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.Types of Data CollectedPersonal DataWhile using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:Email addressFirst name and last nameCookies and Usage DataUsage DataWe may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.Tracking & Cookies DataWe use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.Examples of Cookies we use:Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.Use of Dataxorsyst.com uses the collected data for various purposes:To provide and maintain the ServiceTo notify you about changes to our ServiceTo allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do soTo provide customer care and supportTo provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the ServiceTo monitor the usage of the ServiceTo detect, prevent and address technical issuesTransfer Of DataYour information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.xorsyst.com will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.Disclosure Of DataLegal Requirementsxorsyst.com may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:To comply with a legal obligationTo protect and defend the rights or property of xorsyst.comTo prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the ServiceTo protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the publicTo protect against legal liabilitySecurity Of DataThe security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Service ProvidersWe may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.AnalyticsWe may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.Google Analytics: Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=enQuantcast: When you visit a site or app operated by a Quantcast Partner, the Partner permits us to collect Log Data from their sites and apps through the use of Tags and Cookies; we also receive information directly from our Partners. We associate this information with a unique random identifier associated with your device (like a cookie id), but we never associate it with your name, email, address, or phone number, because we don’t collect that type of directly identifying information about consumers. We use this information from Partners, which includes information about some of the sites you are visiting and some of the apps you are using, as necessary for our legitimate interests to help improve the accuracy of our products and to determine what advertisements and content might be interesting to you.For more information on the privacy practices of Quantcast, please visit the Quantcast Privacy web page: https://www.quantcast.com/privacy/Links To Other SitesOur Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.Children’s PrivacyOur Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.Changes To This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:By email: xorsystdotcom@yahoo.comBy visiting this page on our website: http://xorsyst.com/contact/
Your source for everything cool from Japan including Japanese pop culture, anime, manga, schoolgirls, fanservice, idols, import gaming news, and crazy videos!Contact me
Latest news
View all
Read more
Perfect yakitori from a machine?
Read more
Japanese Idols Try English Accent
Read more
Everything we know about Detective Pikachu!
Read more
Japan unveils a Nutella vending machine! Sugoi SitesBlack TokyoDannychooJamaipanese.comTwitch – EyeZxPTwitch – JuanernestoTwitch – RalphJaysonTwitch – RemylebaeTwitch – SpiceoflifeWhat Japan ThinksTags
Work97new75school51site49Japan47cam47guys41tho38nicola38happy38Anime37cool36again35funny31gaming28ddr26missing26Life26coming25japanese23
© xorsyst.com 2001. Some Rights Reserved (Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License) Privacy PolicyThis site is protected by reCAPTCHA and the Google Privacy Policy and Terms of Service apply.
